<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Kristian's Portfolio</title><link>https://kristian-94.github.io/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Kristian's Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kristian-94.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating Moodle Tips</title><link>https://kristian-94.github.io/projects/moodletips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kristian-94.github.io/projects/moodletips/</guid><description>A Youtube channel, online course and community centered around Moodle development and training.
The problem When I started trying to learn Moodle, the code and ecosystem around it was very hard to understand. The documentation is also not clear unless you already know Moodle!
I am passionate about teaching and sharing knowledge. This project is my small contribution to make a mark on the Moodle world and help new developers get up to scratch.</description></item><item><title>Creating the Logbook Project</title><link>https://kristian-94.github.io/projects/logbook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kristian-94.github.io/projects/logbook/</guid><description>Track billed hours to separate buckets
The problem Keeping track of the ‘real’ hours worked vs the adjusted ‘billed’ hours can be tricky. They are different, and we need a system to keep track of billed hours. This is for companies that have clients that buy ‘Buckets’ of hours and then slowly use those hours for support and development. Support staff need to be able to answer the question:
How many hours does this client have left?</description></item><item><title>Machine Learning</title><link>https://kristian-94.github.io/projects/micrograd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kristian-94.github.io/projects/micrograd/</guid><description>These are my notes taken during implementing the micrograd library and training a neural net to recognise images.
Check back soon for a link to a working demo and code :)
What is micrograd? This is all based off Andrej Karpathy&amp;rsquo;s Github repo and Youtube videos. I am a huge fan of him!
Micrograd is all you need to train neural networks. Everything else (pytorch/tensor flow) is just efficiency.
My notes We need to get the gradient of the loss function and step towards minimal value.</description></item></channel></rss>